["Embark Studios presents"]
["ARC Raiders"]
>> CITIZEN #1: A bed down here in Speranza
sure beats sleeping outside.
But it's getting pretty crowded.
[background colony chatter]
[cooking noises]
>> CITIZEN #2: Up Topside,
clean hands don't get the work done.
That's why I stay down here.
Everything has a price,
and it's always higher than you think.
>> LANCE: —1,358 days to make a beautiful—
[radio static: off]
>> CELESTE: Raiders may not follow orders,
but they'll follow a bounty, if it's high enough.
>> SHANI: I wouldn't worry about other Raiders
that much, I would worry about ARC.
[ARC sounds]
Something's going on.
>> APOLLO: A lot of people down here in
Speranza reply on Raiders.
I don't like it, but if you wanna go back up,
you catch a ride with the Tubes on level four.
They'll take you all the way to Buried City.
>> SHANI: Okay, here we are.
This room is the best I can do for you now.
It's a dump, I know, but
you'll learn to love it, I'm sure.
Come see me when you've settled in.